<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Moon Valley Software</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>555 S. 13th Street</Address_1>
        <Address_2>Suite E</Address_2>
        <City_Town>Grover Beach</City_Town>
        <State_Province>CA</State_Province>
        <Zip_Postal_Code>93433</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>US</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.moonvalley.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Phillip</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Hansen</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>info@moonvalley.com</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Phillip</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Hansen</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>phil@moonvalley.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>sales@moonvalley.com</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>support@moonvalley.com</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>info@moonvalley.com</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone>(800) 473-5509</Sales_Phone>
        <Support_Phone>(805) 994-1040</Support_Phone>
        <General_Phone>(805) 994-1040</General_Phone>
        <Fax_Phone>(805) 994-1038</Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>Autorun Inf Editor</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>1.0</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>10</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>01</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2003</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>0.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code />
        <Program_Cost_Other />
        <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>No Install Support</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win95,Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x,WinXP,Windows2000</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>aif10.zip</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous>aif10.zip</Filename_Previous>
        <Filename_Generic>aif.zip</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>AutorunInfEditor.zip</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>114791</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>112</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>0.11</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count />
        <Expire_Based_On>Either/Or</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Change_Info />
        <Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_Categories>autorun editor, autorun.inf editor</Program_Categories>
        <Program_System_Requirements>219K HD space</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>autorun, autoplay, auto start, auto run CD , autorun DVD, make autorun</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Software to quickly author autorun.inf files</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>A program that can be used to quickly and easily create autorun.inf files</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>The Autorun.inf Editor is a program that can be used to quickly and easily create autorun CD autorun.inf files. An autorun.inf file is a required file when creating an autorun CD.</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>The Autorun.inf Editor is a program that can be used to quickly and easily create autorun CD autorun.inf files. An autorun.inf file is a required file when creating an autorun CD. When a CD is put into the drive, the operating system looks for the autorun.inf file. If the file exists, it reads the file and then knows how to &quot;autoplay&quot; the CD. There are a number of things you can do with an autorun.inf file.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>The Autorun.inf Editor is a program that can be used to quickly and easily create autorun CD autorun.inf files. An autorun.inf file is a required file when creating an autorun CD. When a CD is put into the drive, the operating system looks for the autorun.inf file. If the file exists, it reads the file and then knows how to &quot;autoplay&quot; the CD. There are a number of things you can do with an autorun.inf file.

The Autorun.inf Editor was created as a free utility to make it easy for people to generate their own autorun.inf files. With the editor you can create an autorun.inf file that can:

-Set a label for the CD (this label will be displayed in My Computer and Explorer on a Windows computer)
-Set an icon for the CD
-Specify a program on the CD (or user's computer) to run when the CD is inserted
-Add entries and commands to the context menu for when a user right-clicks on the CD</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://www.moonvalley.com/autoruninfeditor/</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL />
        <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.moonvalley.com/autoruninfeditor/images/autoruninfeditor.gif</Application_Screenshot_URL>
        <Application_Icon_URL>http://www.moonvalley.com/products/rwav/images/rwav-icon.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.moonvalley.com/autoruninfeditor/aifpad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://www.moonvalley.com/autoruninfeditor/aif10.zip</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>DISTRIBUTION AGREEMENT
 
You are hereby licensed to make as many copies of the Software as you
wish and distribute it to anyone provided that all files are intact. You
must distribute the install form of the Shareware (you must distribute
the INSTALL file, not the files resulting of an installation). You are
not allowed to sell the Software (except for shipment and handling
charges). Press is authorized to distribute it on any Cover Disk, CD-ROM
without permission from Moon Valley Software. Shareware Catalog Web
sites are authorized to distribute it as a download file (hosted or
linked to the Moon Valley site) without permission from Moon Valley
Software. 

Moon Valley Software * 555 S. 13th Street * Grover Beach, CA 93433</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>READ CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE  BY USING THIS SOFTWARE, YOU
INDICATE YOUR ACCEPTAANCE, OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS

License Agreement

1:  Title to the licensed software is transferred to the customer.
Customer is granted an exclusive license to use the licensed on a SINGLE
computer or computer workstation.  EACH computer or computer workstation
must have its own licensed copy of the software.

Copy Restrictions

2:  Customer may make backup copies of the software for archival
purposes only.  No more than one (1) copy may be in existence at any one
time.  Each copy shall include in readable format any and all
confidential, proprietary and copyright notices or marking contained on
the original provided by Moon Valley Software.

Copyright Protection

3:  The licensed software is protected by the copyright laws of the
United States, the State of California, and other proprietary rights of
Moon Valley Software.

Limited Warranty

4:  Moon Valley Software hereby warrants that, for a period of thirty
(30) days from the date of delivery to the customer, the licensed
software shall materially conform to the performance defined in the
pertinent documentation relating thereto (manuals, guides and computer
aided instructions).  Moon Valley Software does not warrant that the
operation of the licensed software will be uninterrupted or error-free.
Customer's sole and exclusive remedy for failure of the licensed
software to materially conform to the performance defined in the
pertinent documentation is for customer to return the licensed software
to Moon Valley Software and notify Moon Valley Software in writing of
such non-conformity within sixty (60) days of delivery to customer.
Moon Valley Software's sole obligation shall be, at their option, upon
inspection of the licensed software, to within a reasonable time,
determine whether the licensed software has been tampered with in a
manner which would have violated the licensed software agreement.  In
such case, Moon Valley Software will terminate the software agreement
and notify the customer of such in writing within sixty (60) days.  If
the licensed software is defective, Moon Valley Software will provide
the customer with another copy of the licensed software, and the
warranty period will begin upon delivery of the replaced licensed
software to the customer.

Disclaimer of Other Warranties

5:  The Express limited warranty set forth above is in lieu of any other
express warranties.  The implied warranty of merchantability is limited
to the duration of the express limited warranty.  Moon Valley Software
disclaims any implied warranty, including, but not limited to, any
implied warranty of fitness for a particular purpose and, for periods
after expiration of the express limited warranty, of merchantability.
Moon Valley Software further disclaims an all warranties and
representations made by persons other than Moon Valley Software
including, but not limited to, distributors of and Moon Valley Software.

Moon Valley Software * 555 S. 13th Street * Grover Beach, CA 93433</EULA>
</Permissions>
<ASP>
    <ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
    <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
    <ASP_Member_Number>05080</ASP_Member_Number>
</ASP>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
